fatwallet.com 2017-06-06

# Fatwallet Privacy Policy Statement

This web site, www.fatwallet.com, is owned and operated by FatWallet, Inc. (“FatWallet” or “We”). FatWallet takes user privacy seriously and makes reasonable efforts to protect your privacy. We have created this Privacy Policy in order to share with you our information collection and use practices. Please read this policy carefully before sharing any personally identifiable information (“PII”) described below. This policy applies solely to the web site and service located at www.fatwallet.com (hereinafter “Service”).

For questions or concerns relating to privacy, we can be contacted at:

FatWallet, Inc.  
525 Third Street Suite C  
Beloit, WI 53511 

or through our Online Support System  
or you can reach us by telephone at (888) 634-0098, or fax (888) 299-2752.

#### Collection of Personally Identifiable Information

In order to use certain portions of the Service, you may be asked for, or you may choose to provide, certain PII such as name, email address, postal address, PayPal account or similar information. We will not collect PII from you while you use the Service unless you voluntarily provide it to us or authorize us to collection such information.

You authorize FatWallet to receive any account information from any affiliated merchant including, but not limited to, information regarding any purchase made by you through your utilization of the Service, such as: the products ordered, the order number, the time and date of the purchase, and the email address entered for the purchase.

#### Other Information We Collect 

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends.

#### Cookies and Other Technologies

We, FatWallet, and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. Click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html) to manage Flash cookies.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt-out of interest-based advertising, click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads. 

#### Use of Personally Identifiable Information

FatWallet may use or disclose PII to: operate and manage the Service, to provide services that you have requested, or respond to your other inquires or requests. We may also disclose PII in the establishment or exercise of legal rights or defense against legal claims, to comply with applicable laws or regulations, to comply with a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, court order or in response to other lawful requests by public authorities, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, or to investigate suspected fraud or a violation of the terms of the FatWallet User Agreement. 

If FatWallet is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information. We may disclose your information to any other third party with your prior consent. 

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party not affiliated with FatWallet without your consent, except in connection with the sale or merger of FatWallet or the division responsible for such services. 

You should be aware that PII which you voluntarily include and transmit online, such as in online forums, may be viewed and used by anyone with access to such forums. FatWallet is unable to control such uses of your PII. 

#### Service Providers

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

#### Use of Other Information

We also collect information pertaining to our merchant partners you visit, the purchases you make, and the offers you view ("Transaction Information"). We use to provide more relevant offers for you when you visit us or use our applications and services.

#### Social Media Widgets

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, and widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These features may collect your internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

#### Security

The security of your PII is very important to us and we take commercially reasonable steps to attempt to secure your PII. We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. Only those employees and contractors who need access to your PII in order to perform their duties are authorized to have access. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and FatWallet or information stored or transmitted through the Service or on our servers, will be completely free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers, and your use of the Service demonstrates your assumption of this risk. 

#### User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, ask to have it removed from a public forum, directory or testimonial on our site or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by contacting Customer Support. Upon request, we will provide you with the information about whether we hold any of your personal information. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. 

We will retain your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### No Children under 13

We have no intention of collecting PII from children under the age of 13. When we become aware that PII from a child under 13 has been collected without such child's parent or guardian's consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. 

#### Changes in Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time to the reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes, FatWallet will post those changes on this page prior to the change becoming effective or we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account). We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

#### Opt-out

We give you the option to remove your PII from our list of active users completely in connection with the termination of your FatWallet.com user account. All unsubscribe or opt-out requests should be sent to us using the form located here and we will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt. We are not responsible for removing your PII from the lists of any third party who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this policy. 

You may sign up to receive emails from us. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may update your email preferences using the “unsubscribe link” found in emails we send to you or adjusting your email subscriptions by clicking here.

#### User Agreement

Use of this Service is subject to the FatWallet User Agreement located here. 

#### United States

Our Service is maintained from within the United States of America. If you are located outside of the United States, by using the Service, you authorize the export of PII to the United States and its storage and use as specified in this policy. 

#### Dispute Resolution

If you have unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolutions provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

#### Effective Date

This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 31, 2017
